Hello!
Come on, guys! It's me!
Where is it?
Where did it go?
Uh, Geratsu, your eyes are rolled all
the way into the back of your head.
Honestly, how could you expect
to see anything like that?
So careless!
Now how's your vision?
Can you see this?
Here it is, that puny creature.
He's one of those blue sea
dwellers. Is that right?
I just thought it was a raccoon dog.
Raccoon dog?
No, he's nothing like a wild animal.
He walks upright.
That is unquestionably a creature
that comes from the blue sea.
Luffy!
Where are you hiding?
Come on!
Robin!
Hurry up!
This is getting lame!
Aw, where is everybody?
This is where we're supposed to meet!
Guys, come on!
I'm lonely and I'm getting
a little freaked out here!
Where'd you go?
Come out right now!
Scary Creepy Dice Man!
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage!
Have the courage to sail and believe!
And we will see!
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams,
things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see,
and we know that our hearts
have brought us here,
where the compass points our
destiny, there's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage!
We can't stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's unclear.
We still can smile.
We know we'll get there.
No regrets.
Every tear that we've cried only helps.
Our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow?
Where are you, Straw Hat?
I'll find you!
I know you're still alive!
Yeah! Yeah!
And I plan on staying that way!
What the heck is going on here?
What is that?
Where could that kid have run off to?
Strange.
No matter, I shouldn't be
wasting my energy on him anyhow.
I have a more important battle.
All of my strength needs to be saved if
I'm going to win my fight with Eneru.
And I'm certain,
if I use the Reject one more time, my
body will be reduced to a pile of ashes.
It's the end of the line.
Everything's stopped.
Where am I?
What have you done?
You killed our Sanchi!
It's useless.
No pulse.
I wish Chopper was here.
He know what to do.
Sanchi!
It wasn't supposed to be this way.
Hold on, Usopp!
You're checking his right
side for a heartbeat.
The left side is where his heart is.
Ah!
He's alive!
Back from the dead.
I can't believe it.
But he's still not well.
Just look at him.
No!
You can't die again.
I need you here.
Hey, you!
I don't know what you did to him, but you
better not try any more monkey business.
You will stay quiet, or join your friends.
Am I being clear?
Very good.
Who is this guy?
How did he do that?
What do you want to know?
What wicked reason could you
possibly have for coming aboard?
During the six years
I've been on this island,
I've kept your former
subordinates very busy.
They've been slaving away
for me all these long years,
and they've hardly had a moment to rest.
My divine warriors have
been reduced to slaves.
They are most extraordinary.
Truly, they are of great talent.
But it appears that their
years of hard labor are over.
You see, this island is
no longer useful to me.
Consequently, I no longer require the
services of your former divine warriors.
Perhaps you suspect that I have
sinister motives in coming here?
But I have simply come to bid
you farewell, that is all!
I will say this.
Sometimes I envy the blissful,
innocent stupidity of Skypiea's people.
The fools here can only see this island as
nothing more than a clump
of earth in the sky.
What are you talking about?
Stupid old man,
all these years you never guessed the
true reason we seized this island.
The reason that the Blue Sea Flies are
here meddling in the island's affairs.
And the reason the Shandians fight so
bravely to return to their sacred homeland.
You see, all this is happening
for one purpose and one alone.
There is something here
that they all seek.
The great treasures of
Shandora the legendary
city of gold that
prospered on the blue sea
so Long ago gold is
what brings us all here
what is gold and why is
it so important to you
Your ignorance never
ceases to amaze the only
people in the world who
know nothing of gold
Or its value live in the midst of untold
fortune you didn't even
know what the goal was so
how Could you have won
this game interestingly
enough our game of
survival is in its final
play Whoever wins gets
the goal can you hear it
now the sounds of our
lively little competition
As a matter of fact, I'm a
contestant myself, so I must be off.
Wait, Eneru.
The Divine Warriors.
Are you going to set them free?
God only knows, and he's not telling.
Eneru, wait!
He disappeared.
Usopp!
Make way!
Another one!
These weaklings aren't worth my time.
What exquisite ammunition you have there.
Matter that dents does not
naturally exist here in the sky.
The birth mineral called iron, isn't it?
You have managed to make
quick work of my men,
which is a difficult
task to say the least.
First, my guess is that you are
the great Shandora warrior, Jinbe.
Commander Yama.
Good guess.
Now get out of my way!
No I refuse to die not like this not
here oh still alive I see you are tough
Very well as a gesture of respect for your
warrior spirit I will end your suffering
With my secret technique.
Dance attack!
Damn you, Yama!
Axe Moten!
So very close.
Yet, so very far away.
Who are you guys?
That's a stupid question.
We're Deputy Divine Commanders.
You killed our Brother Sartre.
Now you're going to pay.
Brother?
What do you mean?
I haven't killed anybody!
You can call me Hotari!
And you can call me Katorea!
And you guys killed our
beloved big brother Satori!
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but I don't know your brother!
Now you're all gonna pee!
Yeah!
We must deal with these two quickly
and return to the business at hand.
We need to find Eneru and rescue my divine
warriors before the unthinkable happens.
Now, stand back, young lady.
I may be injured, but I'd never
lose to the likes of those two.
No, I won't stand back this time.
Because sometimes I'm the one
who has to protect my friends!
Very well then.
First we need to determine
which tiles they possess.
All right.
Time to avenge our brother!
A memorial to the city itself,
its descendants built it,
after the great city fell.
Shandora.
That was the name of this ancient place.
402 SE.
The city was at its peak 1100
years ago, but then it toppled.
Around 800 years ago.
That time frame almost
perfectly matches the 100 years
of history that vanished
from the rest of the world.
Perhaps this island holds the key the
key to a long forgotten history that was?
Veiled from the world below this is a
complete map of Shandora perhaps I'll
learn more about this blank century if I
go to the center of the city who's there?
Well, aren't you a beautiful young lady?
Where did you go?
A consuming technique, no doubt.
His eyes are rolled back in his head.
And it's really spooky.
Get at you, you can't see the enemy
with your eyes roll back like that?
So careless!
An enemy, huh?
Oh, I get it now He must
be one of Enuru's priests.
Indeed, I am.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Geratsu, priest in
the service of Almighty Inneru.
And I command the Upper
Yard's ordeal of the swamp.
Huh?
Come on, say something, you jerk!
Geratsu, he can't hear you unless
you start speaking out loud!
So careless!
You don't normally forget that!
I advise you to watch where you step.
See this entire area is my territory to
control all around us are swamp clouds.
And once you find yourself
trapped by one there
is no hope of escape the
survival rate here is 50%.
% It's almost tragic ordeal of the swamp?
Best of luck.
It has no effect on me swamp cloud.
No way!
He's shooting something out of
his feet that makes him fly!
That's so cool!
Something's coming out of his hands.
One stinking matted raccoon dog
is hardly worth my precious time.
Take this!
Swamp Cloud Burger!
A deadly swamp with the weight of a cloud!
Once touched, nothing can survive!
Wait! No! Get out soon!
Don't aim it at me!
Please stop!
He can't escape!
I see.
It's a cloud, so if you try to lift it,
your hands will pass right through it.
The more you struggle to get free, the
deeper you're dragged inside of it.
I have to help him.
There you are, raccoon dog.
Swamp Cloud Burger!
If one of those things hits
me, I'll be dead for sure!
If you're still alive, hang on!
Hey!
You've got to breathe!
Don't die!
Oh, good, you're alive!
Thank you.
You saved my life.
Ah, being saved by the enemy.
Pathetic. Uh-oh.
How dare you, Geratsu?
You're gonna pay.
I'll never serve you again.
Watch as my axtile
drains the life from you.
Yes, we'll team up, and together
we'll defeat him. Very well.
This one is called my jet crunch.
The lethal jet dial
punches accelerated with it
allow you to destroy an
enemy before they even.
Realize the fight has begun its only real
defect is that it also destroys my clothes
this is a priest if i don't get out of
here right now i'll end up like that guy?
I've got to keep my feet off the clouds.
The swamp jet things are everywhere.
If I run on top of the ruins only, I can
make it to the forest and solid ground.
Just where do you think you're
running off to, raccoon?
Here's another jet punch!
Rumble jumping point!
Huh?
Bumble Balls last for three minutes.
So, you have Zone-type powers.
Too bad.
How about another one?
Oh, yeah! Weight point!
Swamp Cloud Burger!
Not again!
Dark point!
Why that insolent little...
Weight point!
Rufflescope!
A weak point!
He's gotta have some weak point!
Anything I'll do, I need to
find a weakness and escape!
Jet point! Candy!
Even with my guard up, it's useless.
There look in the clouds
above I can see giant jack
We're close to the ruins of Shandora
Inaru's got to be up there somewhere
Yuko?
I'm right here behind you.
Did you want something?
Brave Kamakiri of Shandora.
Anaru, you bastard!
Have you forgotten to
whom you were speaking?
I am God, you know.
And I know exactly what
you're thinking, warrior.
You're wondering why I came down here.
Mantra?
I don't need my mantra to read
what's written all over your face.
But I don't blame you.
Normally I don't bother to fight,
but this time I'm a player
in the survival game too.
Besides, I'll be leaving this land soon.
I was just saying goodbye to Gonfall.
Professional courtesy, you understand.
A game?
I also don't need my mantra to tell me that
you'd really like to kill me right now.
Very well.
I must admit you've shown
great courage in reaching me,
so I'd say you're entitled to a reward.
Call it a display of God's mercy.
So then I'll give you
five minutes for five
minutes I won't move
a muscle what I won't!
Dodge your attacks and I won't fight
back fry me skewer me I am at your mercy!
Why you but once those five minutes are
up you will know what it means to face?
God in the very depths of your soul.
Speak.
That's the weak spot.
Walk point.
Can I escape?
I can't even see straight.
Still think you can win?
My legs are shaky at best.
And the rumble ball is about to wear off.
Alright, it's time to stop running!
You can beat him.
What do you think you're doing?
Plunk Cloud Burger!
I'm always the first to run away, so
everyone thinks they have to protect me.
That's why they can't rely on me.
I'm going to raise a
pirate flag right here!
Don't you know when you've lost?
Even the air is my territory to control.
You can't escape. Come on.
Oh, no.
He took it off.
That raccoon dog took my shoe.
Throw them up.
I'm coming, raccoon dog.
I'm a monster!
I'm strong!
The weakest beast roars the loudest.
One last jet punch!
I let myself get carried away and
nearly lost control of my mantra.
He only grazed me.
That was close.
Our point!
I'm alive!
My turn!
Open! Run!
Finally I'm one of the pirates' tales!
It looks like he fell right
into a swamp cloud. Good.
Now if he would just stay there.
You hear me?
Don't come up.
Just keep on sinking, you jerk.
He's moving!
He's still alive.
I can't believe I lost to a raccoon dog.
Of all the things I could never live down.
And how did I get stuck
in my own swamp cloud?
This isn't supposed to happen to me!
Ah!
Please, oh please, just stay down!
Sink! Sink!
I can escape with a milky dial.
Wow, he really sank!
Did I?
I did!
I really beat him!
Damn you!
Give me this!
No!
You've got to stop!
We won't stop!
I said stop!
You're unconscious!
We don't care!
These guys killed our brother Scar!
They killed him!
They must pay!
Thanks for the charge!
An impact!
I stored my faucet of flavor dial!
So that's it.
They have four different types of dials
they're using instead of just one.
Ha, ha, ha! That's right! Us! Flame!
Impact!
Flavor!
Ha, ha, ha!
You won't be able to keep track!
Which one is hotery and
which one is Katorea?
What dial is in which hand?
It's so much fun to guess!
Surprise dial illusion! Ha, ha, ha!
We know what they have, but
there's no time to waste.
I didn't care which one of those
puffballs was which in the first place!
Suck Typhoon, boys!
You missed!
Guess which dial's in my right hand?
I fooled you! More parts!
Were you expecting flames?
He's going to ignite the gas!
Old man!
Oh, he's been blown away!
That was a childishly obvious trick.
I'm afraid you underestimated me.
Return!
Cyclone tempo!
You... girl!
Retrieve my gauntlet from the
lower deck and finish him off!
What's wrong?
Did your wounds open?
Forget me, he'll be back soon!
Gauntlet? Gauntlet. Gauntlet.
Gauntlet?
Hey, what's a gauntlet?
Oh, it's heavy.
It's made of iron from the Blue Sea World.
There's an impact dial inside of it.
Use it as I instructed you.
Yeah, I get the idea.
But I can barely lift this thing.
Well, there's no time
to worry about that now.
First out of the event, coterie! You pee!
Now it's your turn!
He's the one who uses fire.
Sopping wet and the air
is full of moisture.
Cool ball!
What's this? Just cold air?
Is that all?
Yep, cold air, and you use fire.
Are you mocking me?
Do you really think a little breeze
can extinguish my flame dial?
I'll burn you to ashes!
That hot air flowing
over the cold air will
cause the moisture in the air to condense.
It'll form a mist!
Mom! Tempo!
What's this?
There's fog everywhere!
I can't see anything!
What are you doing?
What?
What did I do?
I beg your pardon!
And impact!
Oh, that thing nearly blew my arm off!
What do you think you're
doing, you old fool?
The pain will pass, my dear.
But I must say you were superb.
Hey, yeah.
I protected the ship and the crew.